Robert Richenburg
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1942-2008, Series 3:; (Boxes 1-3, OV 7; 2.25 linear ft.)
  - Former Students (Box 2)
    - Puliafito, Tomaso - Westergaard, Curt; unidentified, 1951-2006, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Puliafito, Tomaso
      Randall, Carole
      Rothenburg, Abe
      Simpson, Janet
      Singer, Michael
      Sullivan, James E.
      Ukeles, Mierle Laderman
      Weiner, Ben
      Westergaard, Curt
      Unidentified (Frank, Brother Jonathan, Father Romano)
  - Frank, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 2)
  - Furst, Tom and Darlene, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 2)
  - Gary Snyder Fine Art, 2001-2003, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gifts, 1986-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Cornell University
    Guild Hall
    Heckscher Museum
    Hofstra Museum, Hofstra University
    Instituto Valenciano de Arte Moderne
    Parrish Art Museum
    Individuals
  - Gifts - University of California, Berkeley, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Goossen, Eugene C., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Grad, Bonnie L. and Lynne Moulton, (See also: box 1, folder 39) (Box 2)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1987-1993, 2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition Catalog, "Robert Richenburg: Abstract Expressionist," Brandeis University, Rose Art Museum, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Transcripts of Richenburg interview conducted by Lynne Moulton and of Slide Discussion, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Research Materials for Catalog Essay, 1985-1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Grant Applications, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Writing Samples and Reviews, 1977-1984, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Guggenheim Museum, 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Guild Hall, 1983-2004, (See also: box 2, folder 21) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hasselriss, Mark, 1945, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Heckscher Museum, (See: box 2, folder 21) (Box 2)
  - Hendler, Raymond and Hendler Gallery, 1952-2008, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Herskovic, Marika and Tom, 1991-2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Hillcrest Sculpture Ground, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Hofmann, Hans, 1952-1999, undated, (See also: box 2, folders 8-10) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hofstra University, Hofstra Museum, (See also: box 2, folder 21) (Box 2)
  - "Jung and the Abstract Expressionists: The Collective Image Among Individual Voices," 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Hunter College, 1967-1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Instituto Valenciano de Arte Moderno, (See: box 2, folder 21) (Box 2)
  - Ithaca Art Association, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ithaca College (Box 2)
    - Academic Appointment, 1970-1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Exhibitions; Purchase of Painting, 1970-1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - James Gallery, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Jimmy Ernst Artists' Alliance, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Joffee, Sam ("The Camel Letters"), 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Brent B., (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 2)
  - Jonathan, Brother, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 2)
  - Jordan, James E., (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 2)
  - Kaprow, Allan, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Kendall Art Gallery, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Koren, Ed, (See: box 2, folder 17) (Box 2)
  - Landau, Ellen, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - La Noue, Terrence, (See: box 2, folder 17) (Box 2)
  - Lannan Foundation Collection, 1987-2000 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Larry Aldrich Museum, 1964, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Lassaw, Ibram, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Lectures, Panels, etc., 1931-1991, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Leonardo: International Journal of the Contemporary Artist, 1967, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Levin, Gail and John Van Sickle, 1997-2005 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Long, Robert, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Maffia, Donald, (See: box 2, folder 17) (Box 3)
  - M B Modern Solo Exhibition (2001 January 12-27) (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1999-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Publicity, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - McCormick Gallery and Thomas McCormick, 2006-2007, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - McNeil, George, 1956-1957, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - McSweeney, Bob and Jane, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 3)
  - Michener [James A.] Collection, 1962-1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mishkin Gallery, (See: box 1, folder 34) (Box 3)
  - Moskowitz, Robert, (See: box 2, folder 17) (Box 3)
  - Moulton, Lynne, (See: box 2, folders 24-28) (Box 3)
  - Munson Williams Proctor Arts Institute, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1960-1968, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Museum of Non-Objective Painting, (See: box 3, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - New School for Social Research, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Olitski, Jules, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Opalka Gallery, (See: box 3, folder 24) (Box 3)
  - Ortiz, Raphael Montanez, (See: box 2, folder 18) (Box 3)
  - Ozenfant School of Fine Arts, 1949, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Parrish Art Museum, (See also: box 2, folder 21) (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and Printed Material, 1990-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Printed Material, 1999-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pavia, Philip, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Picker Gallery, (See: box 1, folder 47) (Box 3)
  - Pincus, David, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 3)
  - Pollock-Krasner House and Study Center, 1993-1994, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pratt Institute (Box 3)
    - Academic Appointment; Exhibition, 1952-1963; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Resignation, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Provincetown Art Association, 1951-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Provincetown Arts Festival, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Puliafito, Tomaso, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Randall, Carole, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Rebay, Hilla and the Museum of Non-Objective Painting, 1949-1951, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Researchers, 1970-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Brooklyn Museum Library and Archives Brooklyn Artists Project
    Dantzic, Cynthia Maris
    Fort, Ilene Susan
    Henkes, Robert
    Monk, Wendy
    Morris, Bob
  - La Revue Moderne, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rhode Island School of Design, Museum of Art, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Rockford Art Museum, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Romano, Father, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Rose Art Museum, (See: box 1, folder 34) (Box 3)
  - Rothenburg, Abe, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - The Sage Colleges, Opalka Gallery, 2006, (See also: box 1, folder 38) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sales and Price Lists, 1950-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sidney Mishkin Gallery, (See: box 1, folder 34) (Box 3)
  - Siegel, Alice and David, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 3)
  - Simpson, Janet, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Snyder, Gary, (See: box 2, folder 20) (Box 3)
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, (See: box 2, folder 30) (Box 3)
  - The Springs Improvement Society Annual Exhibition, 1981-2005 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Stable Gallery, 1954-1958 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - State University of New York, Stonybrook, University Art Gallery, 1993-1994, (See also: box 2, folders 24-28) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Students, Former (, See: box 2, folders 15-19) (Box 3)
  - Sullivan, James E., (See: Former Students, box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Teaching, Miscellaneous, 1947-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Thomas McCormick Gallery, (See: box 3, folder 3) (Box 3)
  - Tibor De Nagy Gallery, 1959-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ukeles, Mierle Laderman, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - U. S. Army, 1940-1946 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - University of California, Berkeley, (See: box 2, folder 22) (Box 3)
  - University of Texas at Austin, The Art Museum, 1993-1994, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Upstairs Gallery, 1971-2007, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Van Sickle, John, (See: box 2, folder 53) (Box 3)
  - Ver Duft, Lee, 1948-1949, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Veterans Administration, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Vicente, Esteban and Harriet, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Weiner, Ben, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Weisman, Richard and Marcia, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 3)
  - Weltman, Judy and Ed, (See: box 1, folder 48) (Box 3)
  - Westergaard, Curt, (See: box 2, folder 19) (Box 3)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1961-2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Who's Who and Dictionary of Contemporary American Artists, 1986-2006 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Who's Who in America
    Who's Who in American Art
    Who's Who in the World
    Dictionary of Contemporary American Artists
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - YMCA, Central Branch, Brooklyn, 1947-1949, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Zahn Collection, (See: box 1, folder 34; box 3, folder 24) (Box 3)
  - Zaller, Robert and Lili Bita, 1993-2006, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Exhibition Poster, The Artists' Gallery, 1957, (See also: box 1, folder 31) (Box OV 7)
- Writings, circa 1950-2006, Series 4:; (Box 3; 0.1 linear ft.)
  Writings by Richenburg consist of notes, reviews, artist's statements, and the text of a speech. Also included are quotations compiled over the years by Marggy Kerr of Richenburg's comments on art and life. Writings by others are student papers and reviews. Also found are John Day's reminiscences of a painting class taught by Richenburg at Cornell University. Among the poems are one by Lee van Duft about Richenburg's painting Ecco Homo.
  Additional writings and notes are included with the subject files (series 3). Reports, proposals, notes and other writings by Richenburg composed as part of his faculty responsibilities are found in subject files bearing the names of schools where he taught.
  - By Robert Richenburg (Box 3)
    - Book Review, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Notes, Miscellaneous ("Titles (ideas)"), 2004-2006, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Notes, Teaching, 1961-1962, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Proposal, "Plans for Research and Artistic Creation," undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Quotations Compiled by Margaret Kerr Richenburg, 1988-2005 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Speech for The University and the Arts Symposium, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Statements, 1959-2006, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - By Other Authors (Box 3)
    - About Robert Richenburg, circa 1950-2008, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
      Greta Berman
      Edward Bryant
      John Day
      Lee van Duft
    - Poems (by Regina Cherry, Richard Wilbur), 1998, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Sound and Video Recordings, 1996-2006, Series 5:; (Boxes 3-4; 0.75 linear ft.)
  The sound recording of Robert Richenburg interviewed by Madeline Amgott was produced in the course of the research for the Metropolitan Museum of Art's 1999 Hans Hofmann exhibition. Among the audiovisual recordings are: two episodes of the "Art Beat" television show, a series of panel discussions, four years of "Artists' Party: An Afternoon with the New York School Artists," and a DVD of Richenburg's memorial service. Also found are recordings by video artist Raphael Montanez Ortiz, a former student and friend of Richenburg.
  - Robert Richenburg interviewed by Madeline Amgott, 1998 June 7, (1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Video recordings featuring Robert Richenburg (Box 3)
    - "Art Beat" television show, Vol. 1, no. 2: Host, Joe Stefanelli, with Robert Richenburg; Vol. 1, no. 3: Host, Robert Richenburg with Calvin Albert, 1986 (September 2), (2 videocassettes: 1 VHS; 1 other) (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - "Artists of the 9th Street Show Reminisce" (at the home of Marika and Tom Herskovic); "American Abstract Expressionists, Artists of the 9th Street Show: Robert Richenburg," circa 1980s-early 1990s; undated, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - "Artists' Party: An Afternoon with the New York School Artists," 1992-1993, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Artists' Party: An Afternoon with the New York School Artists," 1994-1995, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Artists Roundtable on Art of the '50s," moderated by Dore Ashton at Pollock-Krasner House, 1990, (1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "Hans Hofmann: Reflections by Former Students," circa 1999, (1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Panel Discussions moderated by Dr. Robert Metzger, Director, The Reading [PA] Museum. "Sources of Creativity: A Discussion by New York Artists" and "Growth of Artistic Ideas Toward the Realm of the Spiritual," 1996-1997, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Robert Richenburg: Abstract Expressionist" exhibition at State University of New York, Stony Brook, 1994, (1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Robert Richenburg, Master Copy, Unfinished" (unidentified event), undated, (1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Videocassettes by Raphael Montanez Ortiz (former student), undated, (3 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    "Computer Manipulated Laser-Video Works"
    "Film Constructions, Film Performance, and Computer-Laser-Video"
    unidentified
  - Videodiscs, 2006, (2 videodiscs: DVD) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Robert Richenburg Memorial Service (October 14)
    Cornell Artists and Local Video Artists Collections, Cornell University. "Focus on Art: Richenburg" (November 7)
- Printed Material, 1947-2008, Series 6:; (Boxes 4-5; 1.25 linear ft.)
  Among the books is A History of Shrivenham American University; the university was run by the U.S. Army where Richenbrg taught drawing while stationed in England during World War II. Family history consists of two volumes by Richenburg's sister, Mildred Richenburg True: The Genealogical History of the Direct Ancestors of the Bartlett - Richenburg Families and Their Descendants to the Present Generation and Supplement to the Books: The Riese - Richenburg Families in America and The Bartlett - Richenburg Families.
  Additional printed material is found among the subject files (series 3)
  - Advertisements for Richenburg Exhibitions, 1950s-2007, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Articles about/mentioning Richenburg, 1949-1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Articles about/mentioning Richenburg, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Articles about/mentioning Richenburg, 1963-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Articles about/mentioning Richenburg, 1999-2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Articles about/mentioning Richenburg, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Books, 1946-1984, (2 vols.; See also: box 5, folder 15) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Course Brochures, Robert Richenburg, instructor, 1947-1950, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements (Box 4)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1948-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Richenburg Solo and Group Exhibitions, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Richenburg on Jury, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Family History, 1991-1993, (2 vols.) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Membership Lists, Artists Equity Association, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, 1950-1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Press Release, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook, 1949-1981, (includes photocopies) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Student Handbook, Ithaca College (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Photographs, circa 1923-2006, Series 7:; (Boxes 5-6; 0.45 linear ft.)
  In addition to paintings and sculpture by Richenburg, images of art work include a rock garden that he construccted on his swimming pool deck. Exhbitions documented are retrospectives held at Colgate University and Guild Hall Musuem. In addition to Robert Richenburg and his family, photographs of people include friends, dealers, curators, his assistant, and other artists; among the artists are those represented by David Findlay Jr. Gallery. Views of places are Richenburg's boyhood home in Roslindale, MA and his house in Ithaca, NY.
  Many World War II photographs taken in France and England are very small snapshots. They contain images of artwork, people, places, and miscellaneous subjects. Artwork is not by Richenburg. Images of people include Richenburg, several group shots, and other individuals, both identified and unidentified. Also found are many views of Shrivenham American University.
  Additional photographs are scattered throughout the subject files (series 3), and a small number appear as enclosures with correspondence (series 2).
  - Art Work by Robert Richenburg (Box 5)
    - Paintings and Sculpture by Robert Richenburg (A-Z, untitled), 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Rock Garden, Swimming Pool Deck (Martha Albert, photographer), circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Rock Garden, Swimming Pool Deck (Bill Ashworth, photographer), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Events (Box 5)
    - "Artists Roundtable on Art of the '50s," Pollock-Krasner House, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Dore Ashton (moderator)
      Herman Cherry
      Sidney Geist
      Ray Hendler
      Ibram and Ernestine Lassaw
      Mercedes Matter
      Robert Richenburg
      David Slivka
    - Exhibition Openings-Robert Richenburg with Friends and Colleagues, 1984-2003 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Bologna/Landi Gallery (1984)
      M B Modern Gallery (2001 January 11)
      David Findlay Jr. Fine Art (2001 January 12)
      McCormick Gallery (2002 May 3)
      David Findlay Jr. Fine Art (2003 February 8)
  - Party for Tibetan Monks at Richenburg's Home, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Seminar at Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Installations (Box 5)
    - "Robert Richenburg: A Selective Review of Painting and Sculpture, 1950-1970," The Picker Gallery, Colgate University, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Robert Richenburg: A Fifty Year Survey," Guild Hall Museum, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - People (Box 5)
    - Robert Richenburg, circa 1923-1935 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Robert Richenburg, circa 1942-1966 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Robert Richenburg, 1972-1984 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Robert Richenburg, 1990-2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Robert Richenburg with siblings Fred, Millie, Betty; and parents, Frederick Henry and Spray Edna Bartlett Richenburg, pre-1960; circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Robert Richenburg with Libby Chic Peltyn Richenburg and son Ronald, 1948-1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Robert Richenburg and Libby Chic Peltyn Richenburg with Walter P. Chrysler, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Robert Richenburg with Margaret (Marggy) Kerr, 1980-2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Robert Richenburg with Margaret (Marggy) Kerr and Family, 1985-2006 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Robert Richenburg with Friends in Provincetown, MA, 1952-1953, (a CD containing all images is included) (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Giorgio Cavallon
      Franz Kline
      Ernestine and Ibram Lassaw
      Philip and Marcia Pavia
      James Rosali
      Iska and Joop Sander
    - Robert Richenburg with Others, 1970-2005, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Arronis (Richenburg's assistant)
      Molly Barnes
      Paul Brach
      Arlene Bujese
      Ron Delsener
      Dallas Dunn
      Marika Herskovic
      Jim Jordan
      Mark Kostabi
      Ellen Landau
      Katie Leonard
      Gail Levin
      Thomas McCormick
      Louis Newman
      Janay Wong
      Unidentified
    - Groups (Museum of Fine Arts Boston dinner; David Findlay Jr. Gallery artists, as noted below), 1966; 2006 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Mary Abbott
      Will Barnet (friend and supporter)
      Charles Cajori
      Bernard Chaet
      Chuang Che
      Lorrie Goulet
      Richard Haas
      Emily Mason
      Robert Natkin
      Louis Newman (gallery director)
  - Places - Richenburg Homes, circa 1930s; circa 1964-1970s (Box 5, Folder 42)
    75 Augustus Ave., Roslindale, MA
    121 East Remington Rd., Ithaca, NY
  - World War II (Box 6)
    - Art Work by Keith Martin and Unidentified Artists, 1943-1944, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - People (Box 6)
    - Robert Richenburg, 1943-1944, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Others, Identified and Unidentified, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Others, Identified and Unidentified, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Others, Identified and Unidentified, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Others, Identified and Unidentified, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Places (Box 6)
    - England, 1943-1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - France, 1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - England and France, Unidentified, circa 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects by Dick Hora, photographer), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)